Guide to the H. Paul Castleberry Papers 1940-1983
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Series 4: Washington State University Correspondence
  - Visiting Political Speakers, 1948-1959; 18 items. (Box 5, Folder 238)
  - University Senate, Moscow Group, 1967-1971; 67 items. (Box 5, Folder 239)
  - University Senate, 1969; 44 items. (Box 5, Folder 240)
  - University Senate, 1969-1970; 57 items. (Box 5, Folder 241)
  - University Senate, 1970; 67 items. (Box 5, Folder 242)
  - University Senate, 1970; 45 items. (Box 5, Folder 243)
  - University Senate, 1970; 81 items. (Box 5, Folder 244)
  - University Senate, 1970; 76 items. (Box 6, Folder 245)
  - University Senate. Representation, 1970; 76 items. (Box 6, Folder 246)
  - University Senate. Committees, 1971; 27 items. (Box 6, Folder 247)
  - University Senate. Constitution, 1971; 54 items. (Box 6, Folder 248)
  - University Senate. Academic Affairs Committee, 1972; 50 items. (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - University Senate, 1972-1974; 86 items. (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - University Senate, 1974-1977; 78 items. (Box 6, Folder 251)
  - University Senate, 1976-1980; 66 items. (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - University Senate, 1977; 67 items. (Box 6, Folder 253)
  - University Senate. General University Requirements, 1977; 4 items. (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - University Senate, 1978; 44 items. (Box 6, Folder 255)
  - University Senate, 1978; 27 items. (Box 6, Folder 256)
  - University Senate, 1979; 59 items. (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - University Senate, 1979; 90 items. (Box 6, Folder 258)
  - University Senate, 1980; 66 items. (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - University Senate, 1980; 66 items. (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - University Senate, 1981; 47 items. (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - University Senate, 1981; 50 items. (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - University Senate, 1981; 76 items. (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - University Senate, 1980-1982; 84 items. (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - University Senate, 1982; 54 items. (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - University Senate, 1983; 80 items. (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - University Senate, 1983; 67 items. (Box 6, Folder 267)
  - University Teaching: Methods and Evaluation, 1976-1981; 76 items. (Box 6, Folder 268)
- Series 5: American Government
  - Subseries 5.1: Local and State Government
    - Book Reviews, 1957-1982 (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Book Reviews, 1957-1982 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Correspondence Regarding Textbook Publishing, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - County Caucus and Convention System, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - Election, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 273)
    - Gallup Poll Questions, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 274)
    - Invited Address: "Myth and Reality In American Foreign Policy, Washington State University, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 275)
    - Letters To The Editor, Newspaper Interviews of H. Paul Castleberry, 1950-1968 (Box 7, Folder 276)
    - Ninth Legislative District Democratic Council, 1981-1988 (Box 7, Folder 277)
    - Publications of H. Paul Castleberry, 1947-1966 (Box 7, Folder 278)
    - State Democratic Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - State Democratic Convention, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Western Political Quarterly, 1957-1963 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - Whitman County Democratic Party, 1984-1989 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - Whitman County Elections, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Whitman County Political Maps, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 284)
  - Subseries 5.2: Federal and State Government
    - Administration and Civil Service, 1978-1981 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Congress, 1961-1978 (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Elections and Election Reform, Primaries, 1974-1984 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Executive: Richard Nixon, 1974-1981 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - Executive: Ronald Reagan, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Finance and Budget, 1949-1982 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - Impeachment, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - Jewish People and Politics, 1960-1982 (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - Loyalty, 1947-1978 (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - McCarthyism, 1951-1968 (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - Territories, 1952-1978 (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - Vice-President, 1978-1982 (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - Watergate, 1976-1982 (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - Subseries 5.3: Functions of Federal Government
    - Agriculture, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Atoms for Peace, 1965-1982 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Business Regulation, 1960-1982 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Education, 1961-1984 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - Environment and Land, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - Housing, 1977-1981 (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - Social Security and Welfare, 1969-1980 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - Taxes and Tax Evasion, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 305)
  - Subseries 5.4: State Government
    - Attorney-General, 1958-1970 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - Constitution, State of Washington, 1965-1977 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Courts, 1947-1982 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Conventions, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Election Ballots, Washington State, 1956-1964 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Elections, 1947-1983 (Box 8, Folder 311)
    - Elections and Conventions, 1956-1960 (Box 8, Folder 312)
    - Finance, 1964-1978 (Box 8, Folder 313)
    - Governor and Administration, 1952-1981 (Box 8, Folder 314)
    - Legislature, 1956-1984 (Box 8, Folder 315)
    - Local Government, 1958-1982 (Box 8, Folder 316)
    - Personnel, 1963-1974 (Box 8, Folder 317)
    - Political Parties, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 318)
    - Pressure Groups, Public Disclosure, 1976-1981 (Box 8, Folder 319)
    - Syllabi, State Government 236, 1956-1961 (Box 8, Folder 320)
  - Subseries 5.5: Theory of Government
    - Capitalism, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 321)
    - Communism, 19678-1982 (Box 8, Folder 322)
    - Democracy, 1950-1980 (Box 8, Folder 323)
    - Existentialism, 1952-1965 (Box 8, Folder 324)
    - Fascism, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 325)
    - Socialism, 1951-1980 (Box 8, Folder 326)
    - Violence and the New Left, 1968-1976 (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Subseries 5.6: Theory and Practice
    - Citizenship and Alienage, 1951-1984 (Box 8, Folder 328)
    - Civil Rights, Political Science 101, 1950-1981 (Box 8, Folder 329)
    - Congress, 1947-1982 (Box 8, Folder 330)
    - Congress and Campaign Financing, 1982-1985 (Box 8, Folder 331)
    - Congress: Apportionment, 1951-1981 (Box 8, Folder 332)
    - Constitution of the United States, 1949-1982 (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - Courts, 1961-1988 (Box 8, Folder 334)
    - Criminal Punishment: Political Science 101, 1970-1981 (Box 8, Folder 335)
    - Election, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 336)
    - Executive, 1955-1981 (Box 8, Folder 337)
    - Executive: Elections, 1959-1982 (Box 8, Folder 338)
    - Federalism, 1949-1982 (Box 8, Folder 339)
    - Judiciary, 1958-1981 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - Kinds of Government, Includes Demographic and Economic Data on United States Government (Box 9, Folder 341)
    - Kinds of Political Systems: Communism, 1976-1981 (Box 9, Folder 342)
    - Legislative Oversight, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 343)
    - Political Behavior, 1960-1969 (Box 9, Folder 344)
    - Political Behavior of the Electorate, 1944-1981 (Box 9, Folder 345)
    - President and Congress, 1955-1974 (Box 9, Folder 346)
    - Pressure Groups, 1976-1982 (Box 9, Folder 347)
    - Public Opinion, 1961-1982 (Box 9, Folder 348)
    - Public Policy-Making: Daniel M. Ogden, Jr., 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 349)
    - Scope and Method, 1973-1983 (Box 9, Folder 350)
    - Syllabi and Bibliography, Political Science 101, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 351)
- Series 6: Correspondence
  - Accreditation Evaluations, Military Bases, 1979-1983 (Box 9, Folder 352)
  - Accreditation Evaluations, University of Alaska To Southern Oregon College, 1967-1982 (Box 9, Folder 353)
  - Accreditation Evaluations, University of Nevada to Washington State, 1971-1983 (Box 9, Folder 354)
  - Accreditation: Military Education on United States Bases, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 355)
  - Accreditation Missions, 1965-1980 (Box 9, Folder 356)
  - Accreditation: Northwest Association of Schools and Colleges, Handbooks, 1975-1980 (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Accreditation: Western Association of Schools and Colleges, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 358)
  - Administration: President Glen Terrell, 1973-1984 (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - American Assembly, 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - American University, Cairo, 1954-1982 (Box 9, Folder 361)
  - Arab Club, Washington State University, 1966-1983 (Box 9, Folder 362)
  - Brookings Institution Fourth Annual Seminar, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 363)
  - Civil Defense Seminar, Maryland, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - County Auditors' Conference, Presidential Primaries, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Department of Political Science Development, 1964-1982 (Box 9, Folder 366)
  - Department of Political Science Ph.D. Exams, 1952-1984 (Box 9, Folder 367)
  - Department of Political Science Staff Hiring: Case of John Ward, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 368)
  - Educational Testing, Graduate Record Exam, H. Paul Castleberry's Questions, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 369)
  - Faculty Evaluation, 1959-1985 (Box 9, Folder 370)
  - Faculty Seminar, Federal Land Management Agencies, Spokane, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 371)
  - H. Paul Castleberry, Personal Resumes, 1978, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 372)
  - H. Paul Castleberry, Sabbatical Leave, 1968, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 373)
  - International Studies Organization, 1959-1980 (Box 9, Folder 374)
  - Invited Address, "Myth and Reality" in American Foreign Policy, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 375)
  - Iran, Symposium, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 376)
  - Issues in Foreign Policy, Speech at Pasco, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - Lenczowski, George, Correspondence and Guest Speaker, 1968-1979 (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - Letters of Recommendation for Students, 1945-1990 (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - Middle Eastern Correspondence, 1963-1970 (Box 10, Folder 380)
  - Northwest Commission on Colleges, 1976-1989 (Box 10, Folder 381)
  - Northwest Interinstitutional Council on Study Abroad, 1964-1972 (Box 10, Folder 382)
  - Peace Corps Correspondence, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 383)
  - Political Science 101 Exams, 1949-1981 (Box 10, Folder 384)
  - Public Law, Department of Political Science, Jacobs Case, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - Puget Sound University, Retirement of President Philip M. Phibbs, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Regional Archives Advisory Council, 1969-1975 (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - Reserve Officers Training Corps, Military Education Committee, Meeting in San Francisco, 1968-1982 (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - San Francisco Conference on the Theory and Method of Undergraduate International Relations Instruction, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 389)
  - Scholar-Diplomat Seminar On International Organization Affairs, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 390)
  - Seattle, Visitors' Information, 1970-1980 (Box 10, Folder 391)
  - United Nations Interviews, May, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 392)
  - University of Southern California Institute of World Affairs, 1950-1964 (Box 10, Folder 393)
  - Washington Commission For the Humanities, 1973-1987 (Box 10, Folder 394)
  - Washington State University Senate, 1975-1983 (Box 10, Folder 395)
- Series 7: Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging Council, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging Council, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 397)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging Council, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging Rate Hearing, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 399)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging Oversight Committee, 1987-1990 (Box 10, Folder 400)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 401)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 402)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 403)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 404)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 405)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 406)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging: Advocacy Commission, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 407)
  - Eastern Washington Area Agency on Aging, and Planning Task Force, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 408)
  - Whitman County Council on Aging, 1984-1987 (Box 11, Folder 409)
  - Whitman County Council on Aging, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Folder 410)
  - Whitman County Council on Aging, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 411)
  - Whitman County Council on Aging, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 412)
  - Whitman County Council on Aging, Proposed Merger with Home Health and Hospice, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 413)
- Series 8: International Law and Organization; International Relations
  - Subseries 8.1: Teaching notes and-materials
    - Political Science 421, Aggression, 1952-1982 (Box 11, Folder 414)
    - Political Science 421, Air and Space Law, 1959-1970 (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Political Science 421, American Society of International Law Annual Meeting, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 416)
    - Political Science 421, Asylum, 1971-1980 (Box 11, Folder 417)
    - Political Science 421, Bibliography, 1977-1986 (Box 11, Folder 418)
    - Political Science 421, Briefs, I, 1952-1981 (Box 11, Folder 419)
    - Political Science 421, Briefs, II, 1952-1967 (Box 11, Folder 420)
    - Political Science 421, Class Cases, 1946-1980 (Box 11, Folder 421)
    - Political Science 421, Diplomatic and Consular Immunity, 1975-1980 (Box 11, Folder 422)
    - Political Science 421, Exams (Quincy Wright), 1946, 1960-1983 (Box 11, Folder 423)
    - Political Science 421, Expropriation, 1951-1977 (Box 11, Folder 424)
    - Political Science 421, Extradition, 1949-1982 (Box 11, Folder 425)
    - Political Science 421, Human Rights, 1951-1986 (Box 11, Folder 426)
    - Political Science 421, International Law Outline, 1946-1982 (Box 11, Folder 427)
    - Political Science 421, Intervention, 1961-1975 (Box 11, Folder 428)
    - Political Science 421, Iran Hostage Deal, Legal Issues, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 429)
    - Political Science 421, Law--The Limits of Development =, 1956-1966 (Box 11, Folder 430)
    - Political Science 421, Papers Assigned, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 431)
    - Political Science 421, Part I, 1965-1984 (Box 11, Folder 432)
    - Political Science 421, Part IA: Corporations, 1972-1979 (Box 11, Folder 433)
    - Political Science 421, Part II, 1965-1984 (Box 11, Folder 434)
    - Political Science 421, Part IIA: Diplomats, 1972-1980 (Box 12, Folder 435)
    - Political Science 421, Part III: Jurisdiction at Maritime Frontiers, 1952-1977 (Box 12, Folder 436)
    - Political Science 421, Part IIIA: Territory, 1968-1987 (Box 12, Folder 437)
    - Political Science 421, Part IV: Nationality, 1950-1984 (Box 12, Folder 438)
    - Political Science 421, Part V: Jurisdiction, Extradition, State Responsibility, 1950-1985 (Box 12, Folder 439)
    - Political Science 421, Part VI: Treaties, Pacific Settlement, Force, 1961-1984 (Box 12, Folder 440)
    - Political Science 421, Recognition, 1950-1984 (Box 12, Folder 441)
    - Political Science 421, Rivers, 1963-1971 (Box 12, Folder 442)
    - Political Science 421, Sea Law and Fisheries, 1957-1986 (Box 12, Folder 443)
    - Political Science 421, Sea Law and the Mayaguez, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 444)
    - Political Science 421, Space, 1970-1982 (Box 12, Folder 445)
    - Political Science 421, Terrorism, including Hijacking, 1972-1986 (Box 12, Folder 446)
    - Political Science 421, Treaty-Making Process, Bricker Amendment, G.O.P. Repudiation of Wartime Agreements, 1952-1974 (Box 12, Folder 447)
    - Political Science 421, Treaties, 1961-1984 (Box 12, Folder 448)
    - Political Science 421, War and International Law Seminars, Quincy Wright Notes, 1951-1970 (Box 12, Folder 449)
    - Political Science 421, War Crimes and Adolph Eichmann, 1960-1972 (Box 12, Folder 450)
    - Political Science 421, War Crimes and International Tribunal, 1947-1979 (Box 12, Folder 451)
    - Political Science 421, War, Civil and International, 1972-1980 (Box 12, Folder 452)
  - Subseries 8.2: International Organization
    - Achievements and Role, United Nations, 1952-1967 (Box 12, Folder 453)
    - Association of Southeast Asian Nations, 1983-1986 (Box 12, Folder 454)
    - Background of the United Nations, 1943-1945 (Box 12, Folder 455)
    - Children's Fund of the United Nations, UNICEF, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 456)
    - Collective Security, 1946-1985 (Box 13, Folder 457)
    - Constitutional Problem: Voting and Interpretation, 1957-1982 (Box 13, Folder 458)
    - Constitutional Problems: Financing the United Nations, 1946-1983 (Box 13, Folder 459)
    - Constitutional Problems: Membership and Representation, 1949-1984 (Box 13, Folder 460)
    - Disarmament, 1959-1985 (Box 13, Folder 461)
    - Economic and Social Development, 1973-1980 (Box 13, Folder 462)
    - European Community, 1951-1985 (Box 13, Folder 463)
    - Financing The United Nations, 1961-1978 (Box 13, Folder 464)
    - Financing The United Nations Interim Force in Lebanon, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 465)
    - General Assembly, 1957-1979 (Box 13, Folder 466)
    - Interdependence, 1969-1982 (Box 13, Folder 467)
    - Interdependence, 1971-1982 (Box 13, Folder 468)
    - Interdependence, 1975-1985 (Box 13, Folder 469)
    - International Atomic Energy Agency, 1956-1983 (Box 13, Folder 470)
    - International Court of Justice: Iran Hostage Case, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 471)
    - International Labor Organization, United States Participation, 1976-1981 (Box 13, Folder 472)
    - International Narcotics Control, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 473)
    - Multinational Corporations, 1973-1983 (Box 13, Folder 474)
    - New International Economic Order, 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 475)
    - Non-Aligned Nations, 1979-1980 (Box 13, Folder 476)
    - Non-Governmental Organizations, 1972-1978 (Box 13, Folder 477)
    - Organization of African Unity, 1965-1982 (Box 13, Folder 478)
    - Organization of American States, 1957-1985 (Box 13, Folder 479)
    - Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries, Development Fund, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 480)
    - Peace and Pacific Settlement, 1966-1983 (Box 13, Folder 481)
    - Peacekeeping, 1970-1982 (Box 13, Folder 482)
    - Perspective: Concert of Europe, The League, The United Nations: including an in-depth public opinion poll in the United States, 1960-1982 (Box 13, Folder 483)
    - Political Science 423: Bibliography, 1970-1986 (Box 13, Folder 484)
    - Political Science 423: International Organization 1944-1983, undated (Box 13, Folder 485)
    - Reform of the United Nations, 1946-1956 (Box 13, Folder 486)
    - Refugees, 1981-1985 (Box 13, Folder 487)
    - Regional Security Organizations, 1956-1985 (Box 13, Folder 488)
    - Regionalism, 1965-1985 (Box 13, Folder 489)
    - Secretariat, 1962-1986 (Box 13, Folder 490)
    - Southeast Asia Treaty Organization, 1954-1977 (Box 13, Folder 491)
    - Trusteeship:, Functional International Organization and World Government, 1956-1977 (Box 13, Folder 492)
    - United Nations Conference On Science and Technology, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 493)
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization, 1945-1990 (Box 13, Folder 494)
    - United Nations Membership, 1953-1984 (Box 13, Folder 495)
    - United Nations Peacekeeping Force, 1957-1983 (Box 13, Folder 496)
    - United Nations Representation, 1957-1970 (Box 13, Folder 497)
    - United Nations Secretariat, 1957-1978 (Box 13, Folder 498)
    - United Nations Security Council, 1947-1981 (Box 13, Folder 499)
    - United Nations Specialized Agencies, 1966-1985 (Box 13, Folder 500)
    - United States and the United Nations, 1961-1981 (Box 13, Folder 501)
    - War and the United Nations, 1947-1969 (Box 13, Folder 502)
    - Warsaw Pact and COMECON, 1965-1973 (Box 13, Folder 503)
    - World Bank and International Monetary Fund, 1976-1985 (Box 13, Folder 504)
    - World Community, 1961-1965 (Box 13, Folder 505)
    - World Court and European Community Court of Justice, 1949-1985 (Box 13, Folder 506)
    - World Environment, UNEP, 1972-1975 (Box 13, Folder 507)
    - World Government, 1946-1980 (Box 13, Folder 508)
  - Subseries 8.3 International Relations
    - Disarmament, 1955-1961 (Box 13, Folder 509)
    - (The) Normative Approach, 1950-1961 (Box 13, Folder 510)
    - Political Science 322: Capability, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 511)
    - Political Science 322: Examinations and Syllabi, 1952-1981 (Box 13, Folder 512)
    - Political Science 322: Materials and Lectures, 1946-1985 (Box 13, Folder 513)
    - Power: Supplement to Notes of Hans J. Morgenthau, 1956-1961 (Box 13, Folder 514)
    - Security Systems to Diplomacy, 1950-1960 (Box 14, Folder 515)
    - War and the Balance of Power, 1949-1960 (Box 14, Folder 516)
  - Subseries 8.4: International Relations, Advanced Courses A Classes
    - Political Science 427: Bibliography, Examinations, Syllabi, Research Assignments, 1952-1986 (Box 14, Folder 517)
    - Political Science 427: Notes, Part I, 1965-1973 (Box 14, Folder 518)
    - Political Science 427: Notes, Part II, Political Culture, 1959-1975 (Box 14, Folder 519)
    - Political Science 427: Notes, Part III, Impact of History, 1957-1976 (Box 14, Folder 520)
    - Political Science 427: Notes, Part IV, Power, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Folder 521)
    - Political Science 427: Notes, Part V, Executive Organization, 1958-1978 (Box 14, Folder 522)
    - Political Science 427: Notes, Unintegrated Material, 1958-1967 (Box 14, Folder 523)
    - Political Science 590: Covert Intervention, 1974-1978 (Box 14, Folder 524)
    - Political Science 590: Means of Defense, 1970-1980 (Box 14, Folder 525)
    - Political Science 590: Method, I, 1969-1980 (Box 14, Folder 526)
    - Political Science 590: Military Instruments and Issues, 1978-1982 (Box 14, Folder 527)
    - Political Science 590: President, Process, State, National Security Council, 1977-1984 (Box 14, Folder 528)
    - Political Science 590: (Middle East) Seminar Bibliography, 1956-1981 (Box 14, Folder 529)
    - Political Science 590: (Middle East) Seminar Outline and Plans, 1956-1964 (Box 14, Folder 530)
    - Political Science 590: (Middle East) Seminar Outline and Materials, 1979-1983 (Box 14, Folder 531)
    - Political Science 590: Method, I-II, 1971-1981 (Box 14, Folder 532)
    - Political Science 590: Military Instruments and Issues, 1949-1982 (Box 14, Folder 533)
  - Subseries 8.5: Country and Area File
    - Africa, 1968-1979 (Box 14, Folder 534)
    - Angola, 1975-1981 (Box 14, Folder 535)
    - Argentina, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 536)
    - Cambodia, 1965-1981 (Box 14, Folder 537)
    - Canada, 1982-1984 (Box 14, Folder 538)
    - China, 1950-1975 (Box 14, Folder 539)
    - China Recognition, 1976-1982 (Box 15, Folder 540)
    - China, Taiwan, 1950-1984 (Box 15, Folder 541)
    - Congo Case, 1961-1967 (Box 15, Folder 542)
    - Cuba, 1959-1985 (Box 15, Folder 543)
    - Czechoslovakia, 1968-1969 (Box 15, Folder 544)
    - Dominican Republic, 1965-1974 (Box 15, Folder 545)
    - El Salvador and Central America, 1981-1984 (Box 15, Folder 546)
    - Far Eastern Policy, 1950-1975 (Box 15, Folder 547)
    - German Problem, 1950-1982 (Box 15, Folder 548)
    - Germany: Berlin, 1950-1971 (Box 15, Folder 549)
    - Grenada, 1983-1984 (Box 15, Folder 550)
    - Guatemala, 1966-1982 (Box 15, Folder 551)
    - Iceland, 1956-1958 (Box 15, Folder 552)
    - India and Kashmir, 1950-1966 (Box 15, Folder 553)
    - India and Pakistan, 1971-1975 (Box 15, Folder 554)
    - Indonesia, 1965-1982 (Box 15, Folder 555)
    - Japan, 1941-1981 (Box 15, Folder 556)
    - Korea, 1950-1985 (Box 15, Folder 557)
    - Korea: Pueblo Incident, 1968-1984 (Box 15, Folder 558)
    - Latin America: United States Policy, 1955-1984 (Box 15, Folder 559)
    - Namibia and South Africa, 1966-1982 (Box 15, Folder 560)
    - Nicaragua and El Salvador, 1982-1985 (Box 15, Folder 561)
    - Pakistan and Bangladesh, 1952-1982 (Box 15, Folder 562)
    - Panama, 1977-1983 (Box 15, Folder 563)
    - Poland, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 564)
    - Rhodesia, 1966-1980 (Box 15, Folder 565)